[{"Id":6,"Question":"If I ______ stronger, I’d help you carry the piano.","QuestionNumber":1,"Answer1":"am","Answer2":"were","Answer3":"had been","Answer4":"will be","CorrectAnswer":"were","TopicId":14},{"Id":7,"Question":"If we'd seen you, we _______.","QuestionNumber":3,"Answer1":"stopped","Answer2":"had stopped","Answer3":"would stop","Answer4":"would have stopped","CorrectAnswer":"would have stopped","TopicId":14},{"Id":8,"Question":"If I hadn’t studied, I ________ the exam. ","QuestionNumber":6,"Answer1":"do not pass","Answer2":"did not pass","Answer3":"will not pass","Answer4":"would not have passed","CorrectAnswer":"would not have passed","TopicId":14},{"Id":9,"Question":"The teacher will not be happy if we ________ our homework again.","QuestionNumber":9,"Answer1":"forget","Answer2":"forgot","Answer3":"had forgotten","Answer4":"will forget","CorrectAnswer":"forget","TopicId":14},{"Id":10,"Question":"The door opened ______ the man walked in.","QuestionNumber":1,"Answer1":"but","Answer2":"or","Answer3":"nor","Answer4":"and","CorrectAnswer":"and","TopicId":15},{"Id":11,"Question":"I wondered ______ the homework was necessary.","QuestionNumber":3,"Answer1":"since","Answer2":"whether","Answer3":"once","Answer4":"why","CorrectAnswer":"whether","TopicId":15},{"Id":12,"Question":"_______ they go to the airport, they will visit you.","QuestionNumber":4,"Answer1":"So that","Answer2":"If","Answer3":"Before","Answer4":"Why","CorrectAnswer":"Before","TopicId":15},{"Id":13,"Question":"A notebook is a computer _______ can be carried around.","QuestionNumber":5,"Answer1":"which","Answer2":"what","Answer3":"who","Answer4":"where","CorrectAnswer":"which","TopicId":15},{"Id":14,"Question":"Yesterday was a day _______ everything went wrong!","QuestionNumber":6,"Answer1":"which","Answer2":"when","Answer3":"who","Answer4":"what","CorrectAnswer":"when","TopicId":15},{"Id":15,"Question":"Can I have the pencil _______ I gave you this morning?","QuestionNumber":7,"Answer1":"what","Answer2":"who","Answer3":"which","Answer4":"where","CorrectAnswer":"which","TopicId":15},{"Id":16,"Question":"My mother’s company, _______ makes mobile phones, is moving soon from Frankfurt to London.","QuestionNumber":9,"Answer1":"where","Answer2":"which","Answer3":"who","Answer4":"when","CorrectAnswer":"which","TopicId":15},{"Id":17,"Question":"She was wearing a dress _______ was covered in blue flowers.","QuestionNumber":10,"Answer1":"who","Answer2":"which","Answer3":"when","Answer4":"where","CorrectAnswer":"which","TopicId":15},{"Id":19,"Question":"Какой город стал главной целью Наполеона?","QuestionNumber":2,"Answer1":"Киев","Answer2":"Санкт-Петербург","Answer3":"Москва","Answer4":"Смоленск","CorrectAnswer":"Москва","TopicId":17},{"Id":20,"Question":"Когда началась Отечественная война? ","QuestionNumber":1,"Answer1":"12 июня 1812","Answer2":"13 июня 1812","Answer3":"12 июня 1811","Answer4":"13 июня 1811","CorrectAnswer":"12 июня 1812","TopicId":17},{"Id":21,"Question":"Когда начался штурм Смоленска?","QuestionNumber":3,"Answer1":"17 августа 1812","Answer2":"5 июля 1812","Answer3":"5 августа 1812","Answer4":"17 августа 1813","CorrectAnswer":"5 августа 1812","TopicId":17},{"Id":22,"Question":"Когда началось отступление Наполеона из Москвы? ","QuestionNumber":6,"Answer1":"19 октября 1812","Answer2":"7 октября 1812","Answer3":"12 октября 1812","Answer4":"15 октября 1812","CorrectAnswer":"19 октября 1812","TopicId":17}]